{
    "subject": "resource/St._Louis_Blues",
    "predicate": "property/founded",
    "object": "1967",
    "human_readable": "The St. Louis Blues were founded in 1967.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9676610231399536,
            "question": "Before their founding in 1967, did the St. Louis Blues exist under a different name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.942969560623169,
            "question": "When were the St. Louis Blues founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8971846103668213,
            "question": "What is the founding year of the St. Louis Blues?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8114038705825806,
            "question": "Would someone born in 1965 have been alive when the St. Louis Blues were founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7999945282936096,
            "question": "In what decade was the St. Louis Blues established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7640401721000671,
            "question": "What major sporting event would the St. Louis Blues have been eligible to compete in since 1967?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6687555313110352,
            "question": "What year did the St. Louis Blues begin operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6289736032485962,
            "question": "Were there any other major sports teams founded in the same year as the St. Louis Blues?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3454707860946655,
            "question": "How old are the St. Louis Blues as of today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3360273838043213,
            "question": "Is the St. Louis Blues a relatively new team?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The St. Louis Blues were founded in 1967.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6935_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old are the St. Louis Blues as of today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6935_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any other major sports teams founded in the same year as the St. Louis Blues?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6935_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did the St. Louis Blues begin operations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6935_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6935_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6935_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6935_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6935_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6935_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6935_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6935_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6935_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6935_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6935_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that the St. Louis Blues were indeed founded in 1967 as part of the NHL's expansion."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in the documents, which consistently state that the St. Louis Blues were indeed founded in 1967 as part of the NHL\u2019s expansion."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}